[Music]
Advantage Plane, if the rest of the people can also turn on their cameras, then please turn
on your cameras. You guys
can give SBI top up along with that.
SBI also has a top up. If
super top up is not available, then we suggest that you give a
super top up from any other company. There will be two patterns.
Whatever you want to give, if you want to give a
star top up, you
can give it from any company like ICC Bajaj. If there was
not an 18 year gap between parents and children, then they will get it, that one, they will get a
policy generated for them, for
which we will discuss here. And all the rest of the
people who have joined the meeting, I
request all of you that whatever questions you have, you can ask them later in the end
when our topic is completed, after that
we will discuss. Are you attending or are
you listening to me or not, so
that thing means a little bit of
support from your side, then you
guys please do that. Okay, and now we will
start. Like our product,
ICC Lombard, which is a company, is at a
very big level.  ICC
also deals in the banking sector, it
also has life insurance, general insurance and
also deals in the health insurance sector. So, it is simple.
ICC Lombard has
a small tagline, like you must have
heard the tagline of ICICI, 'Zindagi ke saath bhi aur
zindagi ke baad bhi'. Similarly,
here too, ICC Lombard has a tagline which says
ICC Lombard Nibhana Wale.
Obviously, if the company has used its tagline, then it must have been
purposeful, so
you do not have any concern related to claims.
For this, they support you
at a very good level and
if you give
Lombard's health insurance policy to any of your customers, then
your customer will never be
disappointed, your customer will never be
disappointed that you
gave him a policy from the wrong insurance company. So, let
us start on our
topic. The name of the plan is Health
Advantage Plan. So, Health Advantage Plan is an insurance plan. From the
name itself, it is clear that there is some advantage for health.  We have
brought some extra ordinary thing in the market, so
for that we will talk here, first of all
here are the policy benefits, so
in the policy benefits you will be looking at the worldwide tax,
if you give any of your customers a
sum of more than ₹25 lakhs,
then the company
also does your worldwide tax and up to what extent does it do it,
but for
example, if there is a policy of ₹25 lakhs, then there will be a
worldwide tax of ₹25 lakhs, if you
give a policy of ₹1 crore, then there will be a
worldwide tax of ₹1 crore, plus now we will
talk about the second option which is
your tally consultation, the
company also provides you tally consultation for which
you do
not have to pay any extra charge,
it is absolutely free of cost, the company
gives you a complimentary feature in which you do
not have to pay extra for this feature from your pocket,
okay, third is all our
expenses before admission in the hospital and discharge  The expenses after the incident
i.e. 60 days before the
incident are included in the policy, you
cannot make it cashless, this is your remission,
this is your preventive
care treatment, what is tech care
treatment, if any treatment is taken for more than 24 hours of
hospitalization
with the patient, then you can claim on its expenses or the way of his disease,
for that
also the insurance company will give you the claim, the treatment
procedure will also be done at your place,
domestic and ambulance
are already covered in your policy, for which you can use, if
any of your patients or
any of your customers is referred from one city to another
and at the
time of hospitalization, that is, he cannot be taken by road, if
it is a life threatening case, then
you can take care of him and the ambulance,
you will get the benefit here,
everyone should understand till here, whatever I have
told you,
hello hello, you people are hearing my voice,
sir screenshot
[praise]
ok, okay, now let's talk  This is the surface
ambulance service, the surface ambulance service
means the road ambulance, the road ambulance
company charges tax here, how much tax does it charge,
we will talk about that, please I request you people, from
whose side also there is
disturbance, mute yourself,
when you have any question, you
can ask me later by unmute,
okay now let's talk about the surface
ambulance, what is a surface ambulance, there is a
road ambulance, there is one ambulance and there is
another road ambulance, so I told
you about the company charging tax in the ambulance,
plus let's
talk about the road ambulance, how much does the road ambulance
get, 1% off D sum, that is, whatever policy you have taken in
front of you,
one percent of its basic summation, if it is a policy of 10 lakhs then it will be 10
thousand rupees and if it is a big policy of five lakhs then
how much will it be, ₹5000, then there will be 1%
tax or what will be the maximum tax, the tax will not be more than ₹10000,
if you take a policy, okay
and there is definitely a provision of ambulance in it, then the
company will charge your tax there  It will not charge 15000 rupees,
maximum it will charge 10000 rupees. Home care
treatment is also taxed in your policy. The company
also bears the expenses of treatment taken at home,
but what should be there, it should be
doctor recommended. You
cannot take home care treatment on your own,
you can take it only if your doctor has advised you.
Claim protector. You will
get this rider here. You will have to pay money for it, you will have to pay
extra premium. Let us
first understand
what a claim protector
means. It means all the non-payable items. If you
throw it away once, you
cannot throw it away again, you will have to throw it away. It has
cotton in it.
Just like in our policy, you
get no claim bonus. So in no claim bonus,
if you do not take a claim, then
your bonus will increase. Right, but in the same
way, a sum protector rider comes.
If in this condition, after your customer
takes the policy, any  Even if the claim is made by you,
your policy here on the protector's
account will keep increasing till the
time of renewal. It
depends on the basis of inflation
rate, which is the inflation rate. On the basis of the inflation rate of the previous air class
air,
you will get percentage wise
increments of a certain amount here,
which you have to take as a rider by paying an extra premium. It will
not be inbuilt in your policy.
Vaccine discount is a vaccine discount.
What happens in this is that any adult
member can avail the discount which is available for adult members from the
start date. You can avail
this discount from the policy start date, which means you can
avail a discount of up to 1.5% here if they get
vaccinated. And this is for all adults,
if there are two adults in the policy, the
discount is managed here according to the number of adult members, on the
basis of the previous rate. Okay,
other value added services include
video and oil consultation already available here.  I have
already told you that there is also tally medicine,
pharmacy, diagnostic services
which are nearby, health
assistant service is also available, doctor and
kalam and online chat with doctor. If you do not
want to go to the story, or if you have a time issue, then
you can talk to your doctor directly on chat as
well. You do not need to know the story,
you can take an appointment on a tomorrow basis. You will be directly
connected to our homework doctors on tomorrow and
you can take an appointment on their tomorrow basis, you can
talk to them and discuss whatever problem you have
with them.
You can also tell the physical thing about the doctor that you are going to meet here on tomorrow.
Eligibility Criteria: Now let us know
which people can be given this health insurance
policy because it is
very important to know this because if
we do not know this then
how will we approach the policy. Right now the minimum
entry is that we can
give the policy to any person between 18 years to 65 years.
91  From 18 days onwards, that is, after completion of three months,
you can keep the child in the policy till the age of 25 years on behalf of dependent children. Okay,
here the child will be
in the policy till the age of 25 years, but if for
example, there is a child and you have to
give a policy to him, then a child of five years, from
five years onwards, that is, from six years onwards,
you
can give the policy for an individual child also, by
proposing to the parents, mother or father,
you
can also take out an individual policy for the child. There is no
such problem in this. It is not necessary that if 18
years is not complete, then we
cannot give him the policy. We can give it, there is no
exit. If he
wants to renew the policy till it becomes 100 years or 100 years
plus, then also he can do it. Okay,
sorry, what is the term policy already?
You can give a policy of 3 years to your customer together on
individual basis.  There is also a policy that can be
given and there is also a power to give on a floater basis. The
family size
cover for floater is for 1 adult and 3 fixed children.
Okay, the cover for time research
starts from ₹5 lakhs here and goes up to ₹3
crores. Plus, we will
talk about the maximum and minimum tax for barrier trick surgery. Let
me also tell you what the waiting period will be. If
we have a plan up to ₹10 lakhs or if
we have a plan above ₹10 lakhs, then
how much tax will be there in that condition? There will be
50% tax or maximum tax of ₹10 lakhs.
If there is a big combination, then there is a
tax up to ₹10 lakhs. There is a waiting period of 3 years.
Your varietal surgery tax will be applicable only after the first 3 years.
Plus,
AYUSH treatment, whatever the treatment is, the
company does the up to de-formation tax here. The
initial waiting period is up to the number of lakh rupees that you have taken.  There is a
relief of 30 days, there is a tax due to accident, there is
no waiting period for that
relief in any health insurance policy
and apart from this, the
specific business that you have here like
cataract, stone, files, hernia, no
problem, replacement, joint
replacement, cyst, pistol, all these
surgeries will be included in the policy only after the first two years,
plus there is a
minimum relief for free existing diseases, there is a
waiting period of 2 years only, there are two planes,
one of them is Royal Plane, there is
just a little difference in both, I will
tell you about that, you
can take other room category, single
private room, there will be a tax in your policy,
all the tech care taxes will be included in the care policy, no matter how many you have, 12, 15, 20, 50, 100, 200,
500, whatever amount you have, we will pay all of them,
sorry, I have already told you in ambulance, the maximum will
not be more than Rs 10,000, there will be restoration above it.
How much do you get here? One time registration is available.
With a policy of Rs 10 lakh, you will
get insurance tax free for Rs 10 lakh. Plus, you
can avail it for the next and subsequent diseases. There is
no condition whether it is partially utilized
or 100% utilized. There is no gapping
here. If you have taken a claim of Rs 700,000 before
and the second claim comes again for Rs 10 lakh, then
also the insurance company will
give it to you. Its bonus for stem disease is a
very good bonus. The
company gives you a guaranteed bonus here, that is, once
your bonus is increased by
20%, then it will not decrease, it will remain
fixed. You can take a
bonus from the company. The company will not decrease your bonus.
This is the best part. In most of the lines,
your bonus gets decreased. Help
checkup. Talk to the health checkup. The
relief from help
starts from the first air itself
and on that, the company has told you either
0.5% off in the evening or  Then
you will get maximum Rs. 10000 on cashless plan whichever is higher,
but if it is for more than 10 days, then
in that condition he will get lump sum money of Rs. 20000, which
you can tell your customer,
apart from Rs. 20000 for treatment, he will get home
care treatment here, let's talk about how much tax is there on home care treatment, there is
5% tax on short in home care and in maximum, the
company levies tax up to Rs. 25000, it has not levied tax more than this,
these are some of our optional
benefits, let's talk about optional benefits,
here the company levies your maternity tax,
maternity tax is levied only after 9 months,
but there is only one
condition, 3 years premium has to be paid together, on the
basis of which if you are
talking about maternity for nine months, then if you want to pay maternity tax, then
you have to pay Apex Plan, you do
not have to pay Royal, you will
not get maternity in Royal, how much tax will it charge, what is the
front shirt  10% or maximum Rs 10 lakh should
not be more than this Newborn baby
tax Newborn baby will also be taxed Tice
de maternity tax on new born baby means
two maternity tax here the company will tax ok
Vaccination tax is also tax for the child the
company will tax how much will it do
1% of the shot in the evening or maximum Rs
10000 Critical here you will get
critical insurance you can also take critical insurance if
you take this insurance then what
happens in it is that on the basis of whatever critical insurance you have taken then the
full tax will be given up to the maximum of Rs 50 lakh if
someone's policy is of Rs 3 crore then
we will not give him critical insurance of more than Rs 50 lakh
one comes here personal
accident benefits in which death,
permanent total disability and permanent
partial disability all three things are taxed so it will
remain the same here also so
OPD is not taxed in all plans
and this is another option of yours here
if your customer wants  It is that you have to
reduce the premium of the customer. Okay, and if
his premium is getting high then you
can give him a payment option. There is a
copayment option of 10% and 20%. If he
selects this option then his
premium will become cheaper. But at the time of flame,
if he selects the copayment option of 10% then
he will have to pay 10%. If he had selected the copayment option of 20% then he will have to
pay 20%. And
if any critical illness is diagnosed
then there is an initial waiting period of 60
or 90 days. There is no condition of survival.
If the critical illness is diagnosed today
and he dies today or the day after tomorrow, even then the
company will give the money. There is no condition. The
pricing in the plan is according to the
customer's P code.
You can take a policy of 2 years or 3 years.
This is only for 15 days in Helping Finance.
And let us talk about discounting here. So the
discount that you people get in your policy.  The question
will be that if a customer is taking premium for 2 years and 3 years together, then
he should
also get some discount. Right, on taking premium for two years
together, the company gives a discount of 7.5%
and if the customer takes premium for 3 years
together, then he gets a discount of 10%.
Soft copy discount is also available here.
Discount of ₹100 is applicable on
soft copy or policy only. Meaning, if you
go by soft copy only and you
want to take discount, then discount of ₹100 will be
applicable here also.
You will get cashback of ₹100 from here also. And if
anyone has any doubt, any query regarding
recording
difference of plan or policy here and if any difference is
needed then you will have to give apex plan,
absolutely absolutely.
[Music]
Then there is this difference between the two. See, if we get
admitted due to any normal illness, then the
company
says that if the hospitalization is less than 24 hours, then
we will not give you the claim. Okay, very.
Simple but if there are some such processors
because of the advancement of our medical technology,
what is the name of some procedures, the treatment done in that is done
in some time, that is
within the treatment, that is, the time taken in the procedure is less than 24 hours,
you can claim for all those procedures as well, only
some limited surgeries are included in that, there are some
diseases which are included in the care
Ashok Pathak Sir, do you have any doubt Deepak ji, do you have any doubt, no
one has any doubt, no query,
good afternoon
no, okay,
fine, I will share the link of the
Telegram group, you will have to
join it yourself, if anyone else has any doubt, any
query, then please tell, it is
also necessary to take comments, isn't it, after doing it
[Music] address, in that
you have to take simple customer details,
name, date of birth, height, weight, mail
ID, contact number of all the members, all the
people who are getting covered in the policy and what
is proposed in your policy, like the person in whose name
you are making the policy, his Aadhar, PAN
and one passport  Size photo, you just have to share these details
with me, from here the
link will go to your customer's email
and it will be shown through your policy, it is a
very simple process.